David Burt

SOFTWARE ENGINEER

Phone: 04734220521

Email: david.burt.jnr@gmail.com
GitHub: github.com/burtscriptor

Portfolio: daveburt.au

Linked in: www.linkedin.com/in/davejayburt

SUMMARY

I'm a perpetual problem solver transitioning from registered nurse to Software Engineer. I've completing a software development course with General Assembly and gained 500 hours of practical experience. I deliver user-friendly, accessible products. I bring strong problem-solving skills, attention to detail, and effective communication to every situation.

SKILLS

Languages

- HTML /CSS
- JavaScript
- Node.js
- Python

Databases

- PostgreSQL
- MongoDB

Frameworks/Libraries

- Express.js
- Node.js
- React
- Django

Methodologies

- Object Oriented Programming
- MVC/MVT Architecture
- Responsive Design
- Authentication and Authorisation
- User Stories
- ERDs

EXPERIENCE

Senior Registered Nurse

Mediserve Nursing Agency • 2023 - 2024

- Collaborated with multdiscipinary teams to provide client-centered care.
- Mentored students and new graduate nurses acheiving increased learning outcomes.
- Provided high quality care to criticall ill patients in Conary Care Unit.

Senior Registered Nurse

Wollongong Emergency Department • 2019 – 2023

- Consistently ranked top 10 out of 120 nurses for monthly clinical assessments.
- Enhanced documentation standards during COVID-19, leading to quicker identification of exposed staff and patients.
- Senior roles in triage and resusitation.

SOFTWARE PROJECTS

DoseMaster

View Code <u>Live Demo</u>

- Generates realistic medicaton calculation questions
- for student nurses to practice with.
- React.js, Node/Express.js, OpenAi API
- Extensive prompt and user interaction testing

InclusiveDine

View Code Live Demo

- · Resturant reviews centered on wheelchair accessibility
- CRUD systems using Node JS / Express JS
- Google OAuth for authenticaton-required functionality
- MongoDB, Custom CSS
- Deployed with Heroku

Space Station Locator

View Code

Live Demo

- Realtime tracking of the International Space Station
- Google-react-maps, Google Cloud Console
- Overcame 'Mixed Content' error by developing proxy server to maintain secure https connection for
- deployment to Heroku

Blackheath Wind Meter View Code

- Records wind speed/direction at Blackheath NSW
- Ongoing team project, HTML, CSS JavaScript, AWS
- Using Github actions to streamline CI/CD
- · Version control, rebase, branch, push, pull
- Currently converting to TypeScript

EDUCATION

Software Engineering Immersive

General Assembly Australia • Jan 2024 – Apr 2024

Grad Certificate in Emergency Nursing

University of Tasmania • 2019-2020

Advanced Life Support

Australian College of Nursing 2017-2018

Bachelor of Nursing

University of Wollongong 2012-2015